

Phạm Minh Tuấn

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Date of birth: 2 January 1996

Gender: Male

Phone:

Email:

Address: Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Website:

JOB SKILLS

HI, I'm Tuan - A Frontend Developer. I have 3 years of experience working with JQuery and VueJS in which I have created many dynamic web applications and integrated them with other APIs.I also work hard to learn other technologies and update my knowledge to become a professional web developer.

EDUCATION

Sept 2018 - Dec 2018	Nhat Nghe Education JSC Specialized: PHP & MYSQL DEVELOPMENT Graduation classified pretty good.
Aug 2017 - Sept 2017	Nhat Nghe Education JSC Specialized: SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION (SEO) Graduation classified pretty good.
Sept 2015 - Dec 2015	Nhat Nghe Education JSC Specialized: BASIC NETWORK Graduation classified pretty good.
Oct 2012 - May 2014	Ky Nghe II Vocational College Specialized: NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR Graduation classified pretty good.

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2022 - Feb 2023

ezCloud Technologies Pte. Ltd

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- Analyze customer's product and provide solution
- Coordinate with PM to create idea of new product, make wireframes

based on customer's data

- Work with BA to solve customer's problems
- Verify the feasibility of a design file.
- Write e2e automation test code with Cypress
- Code HTML/CSS design template.
- Fix bug all product company.
- Code logic javascript layout using VUEJS
- Follow the Scrum process

*What technology/skills did I use here?

- VUEJS 3, VUE COMPOSITION API, VUE Typescript, HTML/CSS, Ant Design UI, Bootstrap 4, Flutter, Web Design · UX Research · Material-UI, Cypress

April 2021 - June 2022

ROWBOAT SOFTWARE COMPANY

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- Code HTML/CSS design template
- Fix bug all product company.
- Code logic javascript layout using VUEJS
- Follow the Scrum process

*What technology/skills did I use here?

- VUEJS 3, VUE COMPOSITION API, VUE Typescript, HTML/CSS, Ant Design UI, Bootstrap 4.

July 2020 - April 2021

JSC

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- Handling tasks taken down from superiors.
- Programming interfaces and web applications according to customer requirements.
- Fix bugs arising in the project.
- Convert Template PSD, Figma to HTML/CSS and loop data.
- Write Javascript ES6 Jquery code to build scripts for the web.
- working with api php.

July 2017 - Dec 2019

ABM DISTRIBUTION COMPANY

SEO & WEBMASTERS

*Seo onpage and offpage for company website:

- Long-term planning and conduct seo onpage on the company website with .Net system.
- Keyword planning and research to conduct S.E.O offpage.
- Optimize and build backlinks on web 2.0 and forums.
- Content seeding to get more traffic to the web.

*Administration and redesign of the site under the direction of superiors:

- Make a list of items and functions that need to be redesigned into excel file and send to outsourcing partners to complete the website.
- Adjust the subject by HTML / CSS code as required by superiors.
- Manage hosting services and domain names of corporate websites

*Manage e-commerce platforms (Shopee, Lazada, Sendo, Tiki):

- Research policies of e-commerce merchant providers.
- Post the company's products into e-commerce vendors.
- Working with the e-commerce provider's e-commerce partner via phone and zalo.
- Optimize e-commerce goods

SKILLS

Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint
Programming Language	Html/CSS, Javascript ES6, PHP & MySQL, Vuejs, jQuery,Github. Bootstrap 4, Sass
Tools Design	Photoshop, Figma, XD